https://www.montenido.com/privacy-policy/

Monte NidoAbout UsWhy Monte Nido?Trusted OutcomesLeadership TeamLocationsResidential TreatmentAgoura Hills, CAEast Bay, CAMalibu, CAChicago, ILBoston, MAGlenwood, MDGlen Cove, NYIrvington, NYEugene, ORAtlanta, GAPortland, ORPartial Hospitalization ProgrammingLos Angeles, CANewport Beach, CABoston, MANew York, NYWestchester, NYEugene, ORPortland, ORPhiladelphia, PAProgramsResidential TreatmentPartial Hospitalization ProgrammingAlumnae ServicesVirtual ProgrammingTreatmentWhat We TreatMedical & Nursing OversightNutrition & FoodCo-Occurring PresentationsExercise & MovementFamily Work and Life-Enhancing ExperiencesAdmissionsAdmitting to Monte NidoFinancial ConsiderationsReferring ProvidersResourcesEducation and ResourcesFamily ResourcesBlogCareersContact UsContact UsMediaMonte Nido & Affiliates Call Today. We are here to help. 888.228.1253About UsWhy Monte Nido?Trusted OutcomesLeadership TeamLocationsResidential TreatmentAgoura Hills, CAEast Bay, CAMalibu, CAChicago, ILBoston, MAGlenwood, MDGlen Cove, NYIrvington, NYEugene, ORAtlanta, GAPortland, ORPartial Hospitalization ProgrammingLos Angeles, CANewport Beach, CABoston, MANew York, NYWestchester, NYEugene, ORPortland, ORPhiladelphia, PAProgramsResidential TreatmentPartial Hospitalization ProgrammingAlumnae ServicesVirtual ProgrammingTreatmentWhat We TreatMedical & Nursing OversightNutrition & FoodCo-Occurring PresentationsExercise & MovementFamily Work and Life-Enhancing ExperiencesAdmissionsAdmitting to Monte NidoFinancial ConsiderationsReferring ProvidersResourcesEducation and ResourcesFamily ResourcesBlogCareersContact UsContact UsMediaMonte Nido & AffiliatesProtecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to Monte Nido & Affiliates Holdings, LLC and its affiliated companies (“Monte Nido & Affiliates”), and all of their respective and related websites, and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Monte Nido & Affiliates website (the “Site”) include www.montenido.com, www.montenideaffiliates.com, www.clementineprograms.com, www.oliverpyattcenters.com, and any other websites owned or maintained by Monte Nido & Affiliates.  By using the Monte Nido & Affiliates Site, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.“Personal Information” is information that identifies or relates to a particular individual. Examples of Personal Information include, among others, name, email address, phone number, mailing address, and online identifiers.Collection of your Personal InformationIn order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Monte Nido & Affiliates may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:–           First and Last Name;–           E-mail Address;–           Phone Number;–           IP address.We do not collect any Personal Information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us, including when you contact us directly, or as discussed below, with regarding to tracking your behavior on our Site. However, you may be required to provide certain Personal Information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. For example, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-Personal Information in the future.Use of your Personal InformationMonte Nido & Affiliates collects and uses your Personal Information to operate its Site and deliver the services you have requested.  Specifically, Monte Nido & Affiliates may use Personal Information for the following purposes: providing our Site to you; analyzing, administering, and improving the Site; enabling secure use of the Site; sending information and promotional materials; protecting our rights or our property; meeting legal obligations; and for other purposes related to the reasons for which you provide Personal Information.Monte Nido & Affiliates may also use your Personal Information to inform you of other products or services available from Monte Nido & Affiliates and its and their affiliates.Sharing Information with Third PartiesMonte Nido & Affiliates does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.Monte Nido & Affiliates may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your Personal Information except to provide these services to Monte Nido & Affiliates, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Monte Nido & Affiliates may disclose your Personal Information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Monte Nido & Affiliates or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Monte Nido & Affiliates; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Monte Nido & Affiliates, or the public.If we sell or otherwise transfer part or the whole of our business or assets to another organization (e.g., in the course of a transaction like a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, or liquidation), any information collected through the Site, including Personal Information, may be among the items sold or transferred.Tracking User BehaviorMonte Nido & Affiliates may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Monte Nido & Affiliates, in order to determine what Monte Nido & Affiliates services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Monte Nido & Affiliates to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. To assist us with analyzing our website traffic through cookies and similar technologies, we use analytics services, including Google Analytics.  For more information on Google Analytics’ processing of your information, please see “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps.”We collect the following types of information automatically through your use of the Site:Cookies, Device Identifiers, and Similar technologies.When you use or access the Site, we and our service providers use cookies, device identifiers, and similar technologies such as pixels, web beacons, and local storage to collect information about how you use the Site.  We process the information collected through such technologies, which may include or be combined with Personal Information, to help operate certain features of the Site, to enhance your experience through personalization, and to help us better understand the features of the Site that you and other users are most interested in.Most browsers provide you with the ability to block, delete, or disable cookies, and your mobile device may allow you to disable transmission of unique identifiers and location data. If you choose to reject cookies or block device identifiers, some features of the Site may not be available or some functionality may be limited or unavailable.  Please review the help pages of your browser or mobile device for assistance with changing your settings.Some of our service providers may use cookies or other methods to gather information regarding your use of the Site, and may combine the information in these cookies with any Personal Information about you that they may have.   The use of such tracking information by a third party depends on the privacy policy of that third party.  We do not respond to Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals sent to us by your browser at this time. To learn more about how DNT works, please visit http://allaboutdnt.com/.When you use our Site, our servers automatically record information, including your Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”), browser type, referring URLs (e.g., the site you visited before coming to our Site), domain names associated with your internet service provider, information on your interaction with the Site, and other such information (collectively, “Log File Information”). We may also collect similar information from emails sent to you which then help us track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients.We use Log File Information collected from our implementation of the Site to help secure the Site by identifying potential threats and vulnerabilities and in analyzing the effectiveness of our Site to improve the Site’s function and content.Security of your Personal InformationMonte Nido & Affiliates protects the confidentiality and security of information we obtain in the course of business. We use commercially reasonable safeguards, such as industry-standard encryption technology, to help keep the information collected through the Site secure.  When Personal Information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your Personal Information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.  We do not represent or warrant that Personal Information about you will be protected against, loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties.ChildrenMonte Nido & Affiliates does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children. Further, if you are under the age of eighteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.E-mail CommunicationsFrom time to time, Monte Nido & Affiliates may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from Monte Nido & Affiliates or click on a link therein.If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Monte Nido & Affiliates, you may opt out of such communications by clicking the unsubscribe button on emails.Personal Information Transferred from the U.S. If you are using the Site from outside the United States, please be aware that Personal Information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States. Although we take steps to provide adequate safeguards, the data protection laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using the Site, you consent to your information being transferred to the United States for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.Other Websites and Sites, Including Social Media We are not responsible for the practices employed by any websites or services linked to or from our Site, including the information or content contained within them.  A link to a third party’s website should not be construed as an endorsement.  We encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing Personal Information to third parties.Changes to this StatementMonte Nido & Affiliates reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.Contact InformationMonte Nido & Affiliates welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Monte Nido & Affiliates has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Monte Nido & Affiliates at:Monte Nido & Affiliates Holdings, LLC6100 SW 76th StreetMiami, Florida 33143Email Address:stayconnected@montenidoaffiliates.comTelephone number:305-663-1876Effective as of July 1, 2020
